Nostalgia, that's why you're here
your tourist in your own youth
Just cuz you had a near-death experience. Now, you're feeling all fuzzy and warm
What other moments we'll be revisiting?
Here's a good one, how about the time you sold Tommy his very first hit?
Leading him onto heroin addiction HIV infection and ultimately his death
Aye that's mine, how's yours?
She'd be a woman by now
Maybe kids of her own. But she never got that far did she?
Never got to lead her life
Because her father, someone who should have been looking after her
Protecting his own infant was too busy filling his own veins with heroin
To check that she was breathing properly
choose life
We're going for a walk.
What?
A walk
oh Fuck
Choose life, choose a job, choose a career, choose a family, choose a fucking big television
choose washing machines, cars, Compact Disc players, and electrical tin openers
Choose group health low cholesterol and dental insurance
Choose fixed-interest mortgage repayments, choose a starter home choose your friends
Choose your future choose life